Jaturong Duangchaiyusuk, Team Lead & Senior Developer

Email: jaturong.duang@gmail.com Mobile: (+66) 86 906 8319

Date of Birth: 6 Feb 1990 Nationality: Thai Gender: Male

Github: https://github.com/srankmeng

Summary / Profile:

I am a team lead & web developer who wants to improve my skill always. I have several experiences with software development. For technical skills such as frontend, backend, automated testing, and AWS services (EC2, S3, Lambda, Cloudfront, etc.). For other skills, I used to use the Agile process in my projects which have planning, backlogs refinement, daily stand up, and retrospective. And I can use tools that are related to my tasks. In addition, I supported the team like a review code, coaching team members and finding the solutions when having some problems for delivering tasks on time for team success.

Employment History:

May 2021 - Jul 2022

Team Lead Developer, Redlamp Co., Ltd.

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & clear issue block for delivering the project on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Nest js for web development
- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Use Cypress for E2E automate part
- The delivery website which client site and back-office site

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Senior Backend Developer, SCB

Bangkok, Thailand

- Join in Robinhood application team
- Develop API in OTA feature (online travel agency), connect 3rd party api
- Maintain existing feature
- Use AWS service for support the feature
- Develop the unit test for support the feature
- · Meeting and discussing with team

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021

Team Lead Developer, SCG

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery projects on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Flask for web development

- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Delivery website https://www.scg-id.com that including back-office site

Jan 2017 - Dec 2019

Frontend Team Lead & Senior Developer, Lqid 360 Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery projects on time
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use React, Redux for frontend web development
- Motivation team members and made teamwork
- Use jest for unit test
- Discussing with backend team for design response api
- Delivery KYC's back-office
- Delivery chat system use in back-office with WebRTC technology
- Delivery monitoring system display with chart

May 2012 - Dec 2016

Frontend Developer

Bangkok, Thailand

- Created HTML & CSS related to designs
- Use jquery to manage data on the frontend side
- Use Angularjs v1 to manage data on the frontend side
- Integrate API and display data
- Delivery BigC check QC back-office
- Delivery E-commerce web
- Support team & issues

Educations:

May 2008 - Apr 2012

Computer Engineering Bachelor's Degree Bangkok, Thailand King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang (KMITL)

Skills:

Javascript Jest Skillful Expert Vue, Nuxt Docker Expert Experienced **AWS** React, Redux Skillful Experienced **React Native** Skillful Github Action Skillful Html & Css Agile Expert Experienced Jquery Odoo Skillful Expert Bootstrap MongoDB Skillful Expert Nest js, Node js PostgresSQL & MySQL Skillful Experienced **Typescript** Cypress Skillful Experienced

	Python	Skillful	Git	Expert
	Liff	Skillful	Firebase	Skillful
Languages:	Thai	Native	English	good command

Hobbies:

Cinema, Japanese manga, Watching football, Beer